Guide to the James B. Hunt Papers
James B. Hunt Papers
- Documents, 1971-1972, 1977-1996, and undated
  - "A North Carolina Agenda for Action" (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - "A North Carolina Agenda for Action" (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Minorities Brochure, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Veterans Letter Mailing, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Issue Paper, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Actuality Scripts, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Smart Fax Documentation, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Actualities, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clipping, Debates, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Polls (Hunt and Gardner), 1992 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, polls, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Hunt Tabloid, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Hunt Forum Appearance Schedule, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - List of Businesses Contributing to Jim Gardner, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Clippings on Jim Gardner: Negative Campaigning, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Hunt Campaign Literature, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - County Ad Slicks, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Thornburg, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Financial Reports, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Letters to Editor, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Hunt - Abortion, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Hunt - Children, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Hunt - Business Record, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Direct Mail - Gardner Business, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Hunt - Education Rhetoric, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Hunt - Crime Response, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Roy Lee Fox, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Hunt - Environment Rhetoric, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Hunt - Issues Overview, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Hunt - Prison Bonds, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Hunt - Stump Speech, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Nursing Homes, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Transportation Reform, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Notes and Memorandums, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - General Fund Revenue Forecast, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings - Jim Gardner, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Research tasks, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - AIDS research, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Crime research, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - "A North Carolina Agenda for Action" (Jim Hunt campaign booklet), 1992 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Inauguration, 1993 January (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1994-1995 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Ed Turlington's (Hunt campaign manager) Corresepondence, 1996 February-March (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Cabarrus County, 1996 February, May (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Chatham County, 1996 February-April (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Cumberland County, 1996 February (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Durham County, 1996 February-March (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Gaston County, 1996 February, June (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Hunt Correspondence: New Hanover County, 1996 February-March (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Pasquotank County, 1996 February-July (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Surry County, 1996 February (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Wake County, 1996 February-June (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Wilson County, 1996 February (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Buncombe County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Duplin County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Gates County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Madison County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Martin County, 1996 March-April (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Mecklenburg County, 1996 March-June (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Orange County, 1996 March-July (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Robseon County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Union County, 1996 March (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Ed Turlington's (Hunt campaign manager) Corresepondence, 1996 April-May (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Ashe County, 1996 April (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Brunswick County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Caldwell County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Davidson County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Forsyth County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Henderson County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Johnston County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Mitchell County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Nash County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Scotland County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Watauga County, 1996 April (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Wayne County, 1996 April, July (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Campaign, 1996 April-September (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Columbus County, 1996 May-June (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Craven County, 1996 May (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Guilford County, 1996 March-May (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Lenoir County, 1996 May (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Polk County, 1996 May (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Ed Turlington's (Hunt campaign manager) Corresepondence, 1996 June-July (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Moore County, 1996 June (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Rowan County, 1996 June (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Onslow County, 1996 July (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Ed Turlington's (Hunt campaign manager) Corresepondence, 1996 August-September (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Hunt Correspondence, 1996 August-September (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Ed Turlington's (Hunt campaign manager) Corresepondence, 1996 October-November (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Hunt Correspondence, 1996 October-November (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Hunt Correspondence: Campaign Supporters, 1996 October (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Raleigh-Wake Citizens Association advertisement, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Media, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - James Gardner research, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Gubernatorial Campaign Materials, 1976-1985
  Items in this series include campaign materials (buttons, T-shirt, bumper stickers, cards, fans, and other items) and supporting materials (correspondence, clippings, invitations, programs) for Governor James B. Hunt's 1980 North Carolina gubernatorial campaign. These materials were received from Governor Hunt in 2013.
  - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1976-1985 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration Materials, 1976-1981 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Stickers, Brochures and Cards, Undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Cards (1 of 2), Undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Cards (2 of 2), Undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Buttons and T-shirt, Undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Fans, Undated (Legalbox 67, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Poster, 1980 (Flatfolder 1)